THE CHARACTERS, INSTITUTIONS,
COMPANIES, AND PLACES
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTIONAL
- Oh no, there seems to be a fire.
- Oh my goodness!
Kids!
Hurry and get out of there!
Please help!
Help!
I'm over here!
Please help!
Sir! Can you take my child?
Ji-yun, wait for me here.
No!
Dad, don't go. Please don't.
Don't go.
I'll bring her right away.
No! Don't go!
My daughter… Daddy'll be right back.
Dad.
Dad!
Dad…
There are still people inside!
We need to use the ladder truck.
- Are you all right?
- They're stuck in the building.
You promised you'd come back.
You promised me!
You told me to wait!
No…
- What's going on?
- What?
- What the heck?
- What do you mean?
- The sun is up.
- What?
- What time is it?
- What time is it now?
What's going on here?
What am I doing here?
Dad, get yourself a girlfriend
and go on dates.
It's TGIF.
- You have to go now.
- Where?
- She's on her way.
- Who?
- My daughter!
- Your daughter.
What? Your daughter?
Why did you sleep in?
You didn't set an alarm?
I did, but…
By the way, did we do anything?
Pardon?
We didn't even hold hands.
All we did was eat and sleep--
Is it good, Byeol?
Dad.
Byeol.
- Let's get on.
- Okay.
Ouch.
I'm getting off.
Going up.
The doors are closing.
That person just now…
She seems familiar.
Where did I see her?
- Dad.
- Yes?
- Did you lie to me at all?
- No.
He must have lied.
I didn't.
Feeling better?
Yes, I think it stopped.
- Did she make a fuss?
- Don't get me started.
She cried because her dad wasn't there.
I could barely comfort her with candy.
Thank you so much for today.
I really slept in.
Did you get home late last night?
No…
Did you sleep on the sofa?
No, I mean…
I cleaned,
but this must have slipped my mind.
I'll babysit Seo-jun today.
I'd be so grateful.
Was someone else here yesterday?
PEOPLEZ CEO KANG JI-YUN
Did you get home…
I'm sorry about…
Jeez.
EPISODE 6
That kiddo is Mr. Yu's daughter?
No wonder.
They felt oddly similar.
YOU DID AN EXCELLENT JOB
You did an excellent job.
A compliment should be done properly.
- Hello.
Hello.
Please wait.
- The doors are opening.
- Thank you.
The doors are closing.
Good morning.
Did you have a good weekend?
Well…
Did you also have a good weekend?
Yes, I had a good weekend.
Except for being kicked out.
I'm sorry.
Did you get home safely?
That's why I came to work.
Took long enough for you to ask.
Your daughter…
Did she say anything in particular?
Daughter?
Never mind. Forget it.
Let me ask you one thing.
- Why did you kick me out?
- Why did you run away?
- Exactly.
- Let's go.
- Let's…
- Mom.
- Hi, Ju-hee.
- Did you get pricked? Let me see.
- It's okay.
- Are you bleeding?
- No, I'm not.
I feel terrible. Look at your hands.
It isn't unusual for a seamstress.
Was there traffic on your way here?
No, it was fine.
Do you have a lot of work these days?
Of course.
You know how amazing my skills are.
Ju-hee,
some people called headhunters--
Mom, can't you just quit your job?
What?
You sew every day sitting here
in this dingy little place.
Your hands are covered with blisters
from working with leather.
Just for a few bucks.
Now, both my husband and I earn money.
Stop working so hard and close up shop.
Whenever I look at your hands,
I feel terrible.
Are these so horrible to look at?
Your hands that have worked
for a long time.
They must find it unfair.
Ma'am, your hands are very special.
Don't underestimate
the value of your time spent.
Excuse me.
I'm here to meet CEO Kang Ji-yun.
Well, Ms. Kang is…
Oh, Ms. Cho!
Ms. Cho, have you made up your mind?
If someone needs my help, I'll do it.
I mean,
I'd like to try.
Gosh, Ms. Cho!
Goodness, I…
Gosh.
Ms. Cho, you saved me.
CHICKEN GALBI
PALGAKDO
It looks so delicious.
Try this.
I'm gonna have a bigger piece.
It's so tender. Try it. Go on.
What do you think? Isn't it tender?
It's okay.
How about some fried rice? I'll order it.
Ma'am, one fried rice, please!
I'm so glad that we found a candidate
for Deluxe Line before the deadline.
I'm so relieved.
Ms. Cho made up her mind
faster than I expected.
This is all thanks to Mr. Yu
and Kwang-hee's hard work.
Did you give them compliments?
Doesn't everyone work hard?
I told you not to judge people
based on your standards.
Then again, Eun-ho is just as bad.
He must have gotten it from you.
Last time, when Byeol went camping,
he insisted on working…
Wouldn't it be nice not to bring that up?
After working everyone up,
you canceled it last minute, Ms. Seo.
I couldn't help it.
I had a prior commitment.
I'm the one who's sad about not going.
You had good food thanks to me.
Isn't Eun-ho an amazing cook?
That, I agree.
The kiddo who comes often
to the bookstore.
- Her?
- Is that Mr. Yu's daughter?
Yeah, Byeol.
Kang-seok told me
that the two of you have met often.
Didn't he raise her well
as a single parent?
She's clever and cute.
By the way,
since when did he raise her by himself?
I heard that they got divorced
before Byeol's first birthday.
- Divorced?
- Yes.
I heard that they were
a famous couple at college.
They got married right after graduation,
so everyone expected them to be happy.
Even Kang-seok was surprised
when they divorced so soon.
They got separated with an infant.
Why did they break up?
Kang-seok doesn't know why exactly.
Eun-ho isn't the type to talk about it.
I think he raised Byeol
with a lot of determination.
Being a single parent can't be easy.
He completely dedicated himself to Byeol.
For paternity leave…
What? Why did you stop mid-sentence?
Aren't I talking about him recklessly?
- He's not just anyone.
- Right… What?
He's not just anyone?
What? You think…
He's my secretary.
I should know about my secretary's past.
Didn't you tell me to be more interested
in my employees?
Right.
Being interested in your employees
without ulterior motives is good.
Byeol used to be a sickly child,
so he gave up everything,
including his career.
He took a leave of absence
to stay with Byeol.
That's why people at work
disapproved of him.
Eun-ho is an amazing dad.
Why did you go on paternal leave?
You were in your heyday
to progress your career.
I wanted to see her smile.
My daughter has the sweetest smile.
She wanted it.
And I promised her
that I'd be by her side.
I was keeping that promise.
Because I'm all that she has.
You're right.
He's a good dad.
That tickles.
If you move, it'll get everywhere.
Okay, I'll try to hold my breath.
Why are you into nail polish
all of a sudden?
You weren't interested a while ago.
To show it to an amazing woman.
The one you met at the bookstore?
I don't know who it is,
but you must like her.
I'll introduce you next time.
Stay still. It's going to smudge.
Are you looking at me with adoring eyes?
You look super ugly
because you're concentrating.
No, Daddy always looks very handsome
when he's concentrating.
All done.
What do you think? You like it?
Well, not too bad.
Wait five minutes until it dries
before you go to sleep.
Dad, you put it on, too.
No, I don't have to.
- Do I really have to?
- Yeah.
- Stay still.
- That tickles.
Ms. Kang, I'll be honest.
I was offended when I got this document.
I didn't lose my number one candidate
and waited this long to get someone
like her as a recommendation.
Did you want to hire someone
with an impressive background
instead of real competence?
You haven't seen anything yet.
Please test her skills.
Any method of your choice will work.
Are you that certain?
I don't recommend candidates
without certainty.
Mr. Jin.
- What is it? This is rude.
- I apologize, but you should look at this.
LUXURY BAG BOUGHT FROM
DELUXE LINE, ACTUALLY A FAKE?
LUXURY BRAND BAGS
SOLD ON DELUXE LINE
SUSPECTED TO BE COUNTERFEIT…
"KNOCKOFF CONTROVERSY"
What's this?
A bag bought from us
was appraised by Luxury Seller.
It was revealed to be a counterfeit.
Luxury Seller?
The one that took our candidate?
Let's talk about recruitment next time.
I need to solve this first.
So what are they saying?
Why do they think it's fake?
The spacing in the logo is
minutely different from the genuine.
Call the customer to confirm the facts.
Then contact the distributor…
What's the matter?
Is it something serious?
The company must be facing a problem.
Gosh, what's this? Knockoff controversy?
Of all the companies,
Luxury Seller is involved.
This problem can only get worse.
Let's see what happens.
But it looks genuine.
It looks genuine?
I can't be 100% sure
without looking at it myself.
If you do, can you make a
definitive judgment?
Here's the bag
that we got from the customer.
What do you think? Is it fake or real?
It is…
real.
The number of stitches, their angle,
direction, thickness,
and spacing are even and accurate.
The lined backstitches are different
from curved backstitches.
Those are also accurate.
Aren't they easy to copy
by manufacturers who customize bags?
That's possible.
That's frustrating.
- If that's possible--
- Mr. Jin.
Please let her finish.
However, it's impossible to copy
the leather coating.
Each brand has their own standard
on the coating of leather.
A tiny difference can change its texture.
That can't be expressed in numbers.
You can tell the difference in coating
when you touch it.
I don't know the exact measurement,
but I recognize it…
with my fingertips.
Mr. Jin,
please publish a rebuttal article.
Can I really trust her words
and take the risk?
Whether you trust her or not is up to you.
Right, but if you hadn't lost
that candidate,
this wouldn't have happened!
Do you still trust him more?
Then agree that it's fake.
Ms. Kang, are you saying
that we sold an imitation?
My company boasts transparency in
importing, clearing customs, and delivery!
We confirmed that there was
no problem during delivery.
Then it's settled.
You say that it's real,
and our candidate confirms it.
There's no reason for hesitation.
Mr. Jin, you should make
your statement first
and send the bag to the manufacturer
for accurate appraisal.
Say you're sorry!
I said, apologize!
Jung-tae.
Jung-tae, are you okay?
Seo-jun, you shouldn't push him.
I'm sorry, Director.
I'm very sorry.
How is he? Is he okay?
Yes. Luckily, he wasn't hurt.
I explained that
to Jung-tae's mother as well.
That's a relief.
Seo-jun isn't one to do that.
So why did he?
I think Jung-tae teased Seo-jun.
It hurt his sense of pride,
so he won't tell me.
Jung Seo-jun, are you
really not going to say why
even to me, your grandma?
Then tell me, Byeol.
Byeol, why did Seo-jun fight
with his friend?
Well--
Don't ask Byeol about it.
Then will you tell me?
Byeol, could you give us some privacy?
Grandma, I want to go
to uncle's bookstore.
Over there.
That's a good idea.
I'll walk you there.
DODAM BOOK STORE
What are you doing here?
Oh, sis.
Aren't you here to read?
Why aren't you inside?
Isn't it adorable?
It's a baby.
But it's been alone for a while.
Do you want to find its mom?
Maybe it was also abandoned by its mom.
Then we can find its dad.
A mom may not be necessary.
Its dad might be
looking for it desperately.
This is a secret.
My mom passed away when I was young,
so I only had my dad.
Really?
Didn't the other kids tease you?
I didn't play with such lowly kids.
I don't know if you'll understand this,
but love is about quality, not quantity.
Having two parents doesn't mean
that you get loved twice as much.
One person who loves you
unconditionally is enough.
Kitty!
Byeol!
Jung-tae teased us
for not having a mom and a dad.
What?
He said that Byeol and I
have half families.
How…
Where did he learn to talk like that?
- Seo-jun--
- Grandma.
I'm okay.
We aren't half a family.
I have Mom and Grandma.
There's everyone.
Exactly, we aren't half a family.
There are so many who love you.
You should have just ignored him.
Why did you push him?
I'm okay, but I did it
in case Byeol felt bad.
Did Byeol also hear him say that?
Yes. Byeol is very upset about it.
You did well.
Gosh, my baby is all grown up.
Still, you should never hit anyone.
That's a terrible thing to do.
Okay.
But one thing,
aren't I my mom's baby?
Byeol isn't here?
No, Byeol hasn't been here today.
I walked her all the way to the door
a moment ago.
You did?
I'll go outside and look for her.
Where did she go?
Where could she have gone?
BYEOL'S DAD
SEO-JUN'S GRANDMA
Dang. Luxury Seller published
another article for rebuttal.
They still insist that it's a counterfeit.
Don't most companies usually stay quiet?
It feels like they're blowing things out
of proportion on purpose.
They're creating a competition
between two companies.
The result will determine
whose appraisal system is more accurate.
Are they that confident or what?
Ms. Cho… Do you think she'll be okay?
I'll call her.
MISSED CALL
WRITER JUNG
Su-hyeon, is something the matter?
Byeol?
Okay, I'm on my way.
Eun-ho, did something happen to Byeol?
Ms. Seo, I have to go now.
Go. You can explain later.
What's wrong?
Eun-ho!
There are people who saw Byeol
in front of the bookstore.
After reporting it to the police,
they began searching for her.
I'm also on my way to the bookstore.
Don't worry, Daddy Yu.
She must be somewhere nearby.
PEOPLEZ CEO KANG JI-YUN
Ms. Kang, I'm on my way somewhere.
- Byeol is with me.
- Pardon?
Byeol crashed into a bicycle
in front of the bookstore.
She isn't seriously injured.
- Just a slight--
- Where are you?
Excuse me.
Have you seen Byeol?
She's went out for a moment.
She'll be right back.
- Dad.
- Byeol!
Let me see. Are you okay?
Dad, I'm sorry.
A kitten suddenly ran away.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Really.
Her wound was treated.
Just in case, they ran a few more tests.
The results aren't out yet.
I'm sorry.
How come you were with Byeol?
I told you. She's the amazing woman
from the bookstore.
Well, I…
Thank you for everything.
By the way,
I didn't expect you
to be the person Byeol mentioned.
I also found out recently.
Go in. She's alone.
Okay, I have some work
I haven't finished--
Think only about your child today.
See you later.
Yes, Ms. Seo?
Right, today's meeting.
I'll be there in about an hour.
Okay, let's have it tomorrow morning then.
Yeah.
Today, Eun-ho…
You met him? Where?
How did you meet him?
Oh, okay.
Talk to you later.
What is it? Has Ms. Kang met with Mr. Yu?
Yes, he went to search for Byeol
because she disappeared.
But I wonder how Ms. Kang met Eun-ho.
That's strange.
Gosh.
Those two seem to
keep getting involved with each other,
or am I just imagining it?
Who am I supposed to blame?
You, since you brought Mr. Yu here,
or the heavens?
What are you talking about?
So our meeting is canceled, right?
I'm getting off work.
What's wrong with him?
What is he…
What is he talking about?
Is Seo-jun okay?
He fell asleep.
He must be tired after today.
It must've been shocking for him.
Byeol isn't seriously injured, is she?
No. I'm going to the hospital now.
I'll call you after I see her.
Okay, you should go.
I feel embarrassed to see Byeol's dad.
- How could I have left her…
- Mom.
Don't say that.
Stop worrying and get some rest.
You were shocked the most today.
Su-hyeon.
I realized today
that Seo-jun isn't just a baby.
How long will you keep it a secret?
It's about time Seo-jun should find out.
Yes, I'll think about it.
Okay.
You know what to do with him.
- You'd better go.
- Okay. I'll be back.
I'll call you.
Something happened at kindergarten today.
One of their friends teased them
for both having single parents.
According to Seo-jun,
it made Byeol very upset.
I don't think
it's the first time this has happened.
Ms. Kang?
In case you haven't eaten.
PORRIDGE
Are you okay?
Oh, yes.
Actually,
I'm not sure.
I think I'm trying my best…
but sometimes,
I feel like I'm hitting a wall.
You're doing well.
At least,
you're always by Byeol's side
when she needs you.
I'm sure that Byeol knows
that her dad is making an effort.
So,
just like now,
always be by your daughter's side.
Excuse me, where is the emergency room?
- It's that way.
- Thank you.
Eun-ho, how's Byeol?
Hi, Su-hyeon.
Say hello. She's the CEO at my work.
Hello.
This is Jung Su-hyeon, a writer.
I'm a friend of Eun-ho's.
I've heard a lot about you.
I see. Hello.
I'll get going.
- Wait a moment.
- Okay.
I'll be fine.
You don't have to walk me out.
How's Byeol?
Oh, she just fell asleep.
Let's go in.
- Su-hyeon.
- Yeah?
Right.
I hope that everything goes well today.
I'm a little scared to read the news.
- Hello, Kyung-hwa.
- Hello.
- Hello, Gyu-rim.
- Good morning.
Mr. Yu, is your daughter okay?
Yes, she's fine now.
I'm so glad. Everyone was really worried.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
Gyu-rim?
Both of you should look at this.
DELUXE LINE FAILS
TO RECRUIT APPRAISER
WILL THEY GET THEIR REVENGE?
It must be an article from Career Way.
How so very sneaky.
Their argument is solely based
on the appraiser's background.
Isn't this a big slap in the face?
This makes it unfavorable for Deluxe Line.
The press was divided equally,
but after these articles got published…
Who's this person?
- What?
- What is it?
Is it another article?
Those famous for
their online content on luxury brands.
They're having a party taking a stab
at this war since yesterday.
They've been running their own appraisals.
Experts from everywhere have taken action.
So what are they saying?
All of them are saying that it's fake.
DELUXE LINE BAG IS FAKE
DELUXE LINE GONNA GO BANKRUPT
IF IT TURNS OUT TO BE FAKE
LUXURY SELLER IS RIGHT,
WHAT HAS DELUXE LINE EVER DONE…
IS IT TRUE DELUXE LINE HIRED
A SEAMSTRESS AS THEIR APPRAISER?
YUP, IT'S TRUE
Mr. Yu.
Let's go visit her workshop.
Yes, ma'am.
GAEMI TAILORING
One moment.
Ms. Cho?
Ms. Cho.
She's not here.
Is Ms. Cho here?
Hello, you must be looking for my mom.
Yes.
DELUXE LINE FAILS
TO RECRUIT APPRAISER
WILL THEY GET THEIR REVENGE?
I had no idea
that the problem got so serious.
What happens if her appraisal is wrong?
Would she be responsible for it?
As a candidate that we recommended,
Ms. Cho only appraised the item.
The appraisal result won't put her
at any disadvantage.
But the job offer might be canceled.
What if my mom doesn't want to work there?
Can she refuse?
That is up to Ms. Cho.
She hasn't been hired yet.
What do the two of you think?
Do you think my mom's judgment
on the bag is correct?
What about you? What do you think?
A few days ago,
I told my mom to quit working.
I didn't want to see her suffer anymore.
I don't know how it got to this point.
Have you ever asked Ms. Cho
why she continues to do this work?
She only took a break of two years
during her 37-year career.
To raise you until you turned two.
She told me.
That's why I'd like her to quit her job
and take a break.
She told me that she was happy to work.
When she smelled the leather at this shop
after that two-year break,
she loved it.
I don't think she's working
just to make money.
She's very proud of her work.
Just like how proud you are of your work.
Stop working so hard and close up shop.
Just for a few bucks.
Mom.
Ju-hee.
Don't you worry. I won't take the job.
Ms. Kang and Eun-ho,
I don't want to do it.
I don't think I can.
Let's just pretend that nothing happened.
Do you really want to quit?
Everyone says that I'm wrong.
I thought you were the smart ones.
I didn't think that it was this serious,
and I don't want to be responsible for it.
We should stop here before
the damage gets worse.
Ms. Cho, do you think that they're right?
Who would even believe me?
Mom.
I believe you.
If you say that it's real,
then it's real.
My mom doesn't know how to pull tricks.
To protect people's memories,
she delves into it and studies every day,
coming up with new material.
LEATHER RESEARCH
NATURAL LEATHER
All her life,
that's how she's lived.
I'm not saying this because she's my mom.
In whatever field it may be,
you can trust…
someone like her.
I guarantee it.
Ju-hee.
Mom.
How can you not believe in yourself?
You're an amazing person.
I know that.
Do what you want.
What would you like to do?
Please make your choice, Ms. Cho.
THE REAL FIGHT BEHIND
THE IMITATION CONTROVERSY
WHO WILL
THE MANUFACTURER SIDE WITH?
Mr. Jin, the result
of the official appraisal has arrived.
The bag is genuine.
APPRAISAL SHOWS THAT
THE PRODUCT IS GENUINE
I told you that it was genuine.
- Ms. Cho.
- Gosh.
You saved me.
I look forward to working with you.
The pleasure is all mine.
Please get up, Mr. Jin.
Regarding the controversial product,
the manufacturer stated
that the logo's arrangement was changed
due to their new production line.
To prevent counterfeits,
the brand changes the production line
once every few years…
I apologize, Ms. Kim.
Regarding the charges
on breach of contract with Luxury Seller,
I'll take care of it.
Peoplez found a better candidate.
Thanks to you, Career Way
lost its position in online shopping.
If I could, I'd make it impossible
for you to work in this field again.
For now, I'll see what happens.
One more time.
You better show something
that exceeds my expectation.
You're dismissed.
- I need to change my schedule today.
- Yes, ma'am.
Is it to your taste?
Thank you making time
out of your busy schedule.
Ms. Kim.
You don't have to walk on eggshells.
You have so many projects.
There's no need to report to me
every time you fail.
I didn't invest to oversee your company.
Let's not meet over such trivial matters.
We're both busy people.
I'll call you when necessary.
Thank you for
putting your trust in us, sir.
You haven't shown me anything
that deserves my trust yet.
You will from now on.
What happened today
won't be repeated again.
I'll prove that I was the right choice.
Ms. Kang!
Thank you for believing in me.
I haven't done a thing.
Mr. Yu told me all about it.
You said that you would
take responsibility for everything.
This is for you.
Ms. Cho's special business card holder
that's better than any luxury brand.
Also,
this is for you.
It's a performance organized
by my daughter.
She asked for you to come.
She also wanted me to tell you
that she's very grateful.
I'll be sure to attend.
Thank you so much for finding me.
Continue your good work for a long time.
I should head back in.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Do you want to come with me?
Why would I? They're for you.
There are two tickets,
and I'm grateful
that you believed in Ms. Cho.
I didn't believe in her.
- What?
- I knew the result.
What result?
I knew that it was genuine.
I asked Mr. Woo to get it appraised
by a few more people.
Then when you said…
Did you think I'd take responsibility
without having a backup plan?
I told you to stay objective.
Gosh, seriously…
It's not that car.
It's not even similar.
We should probably
put a sticker on the car.
I'm not a child. We don't need a sticker.
It's better than not finding your car.
What kind of stickers do you like?
Glow in the dark? Glitters?
I have all types. I can ask Byeol--
I don't want one.
Okay.
How about letter stickers?
Like one that says "rookie driver"
on the back of the car.
Except "Ms. Kang" in big font.
I'm sorry.
You two are rather close.
It's making me jealous.
Mr. Woo.
Does it look like we're close?
I said no. So don't even try.
What is it that you don't want?
Mr. Yu, she isn't harassing you, is she?
Please let me know if you need any help.
I know Ms. Kang very well.
Aren't you coming back from Deluxe Line?
I saw the article. Ms. Cho won.
She won because Ms. Kang
believed in her until the very end.
As I said, I didn't believe in her.
You would have believed in her anyway
without the appraisal result.
Amazingly.
I need to get this.
Please go upstairs first.
Yes.
About the interview? Yes.
Going up.
It'd be good to take it out.
Oh, yes.
Mr. Yu must think you're a good person.
What kind of person is Yu Eun-ho to you?
Mr. Yu?
What kind of question is that?
He's my secretary.
What was the appraisal result?
You haven't told me yet.
HK LUXURY BRAND
APPRAISAL COMPANY
APPRAISAL REPORT
IMPOSSIBLE TO APPRAISE
Is he rubbing off on me?
I was a bit reckless this time.
I can't fall asleep. It's driving me mad.
How did I fall asleep that time?
SEARCH: SOFA
Is this it?
That's not it.
YU EUN-HO
Hello?
Were you sleeping? You just called me.
Did I call you by mistake in my sleep?
I see. Please go back to sleep.
What's the model of your sofa?
- Pardon?
- I mean…
Actually, I have a hard time
falling asleep because I'm sensitive.
I don't think so.
You slept so well that day.
Exactly.
I think that it was because of your sofa.
Weren't you sleeping just now?
When I wake up, I can't fall asleep.
You woke me up.
So what's the model of your sofa?
Tell me now.
I'll take a look and let you know.
What about tonight? You're already awake.
Thanks to you,
I won't be sleeping tonight.
Because of me?
There's something that I do.
Drinking warm milk helps me fall asleep.
Why don't you try that?
Don't expect everyone
to have milk at home.
By any chance, do you have
any other solution?
Shall I read you a book?
It always works on Byeol.
Am I a child?
- You're not that different--
- What?
I'm sorry.
I'll take care of it.
I'll be hanging up now.
Okay.
Sleep well.
Don't have nightmares.
Going up.
The doors are closing.
Ms. Seo.
What? You look pretty.
Oh, thanks.
Are you going somewhere tonight?
- No.
- Going up.
That's odd. You're pretty.
Where are you going
so early in the morning?
I was about to call you.
Perfect timing.
I'm borrowing Mr. Yu for the day.
What is this about?
Heonjo Group is planning on reorganizing.
Mr. Yu has a lot of experience
since he worked in HR.
It'd be favorable for us
to bring an expert.
That's a good idea. Go with him.
Where's Mr. Yu?
He went downstairs to get ready.
Our meeting might end late today.
I'll let him get off work
right after the meeting.
Ms. Kang?
Yes?
Oh, okay.
- Go ahead and do that.
- Okay.
Why are you so dressed up today?
It's my usual outfit.
Good luck.
Something seems different about her.
MESSAGE FROM YU EUN-HO
I'll be there on time.
See you at the recital.
Don't worry about useless things.
Focus on the meeting.
Well, after that was in the clear,
he was interviewed by the executives
and passed through without a hitch.
I'll contact them
and confirm the interview dates.
Okay, that sounds good.
What's gotten into her?
Where is she going?
What kind of person
is Yu Eun-ho to you?
If they keep seeing each other,
it means that they have feelings
for each other.
What's wrong with falling?
You can get back up.
I'll hold you.
Ji-yun, did something happen to you?
Are you aware you aren't focused at work?
I have someone who's on my mind.
Have you checked
why she wants to change jobs?
Dating at work?
They broke up recently.
She's having a hard time working with him.
Get me a new secretary.
It interferes with my work.
He keeps going over the line.
- Ms. Kang, did I do something wrong?
- I'm off.
Mr. Yu, you didn't do anything wrong.
I'm the problem.
I like you, Eun-ho.
Subtitle translation by: Helena Noh